ironaffiliates.com 2017-04-20

# PRIVACY

PRIVACY
 POLICY

                                                                               Privacy Policy
                                         PRIVACY POLICY
This statement outlines IronFX Global Limited policy on how it manages the personal
information it holds about its clients and others. This privacy applies to all website users,
whether you are our former, existing or potential client or just a visitor of our website.
Your privacy is of the upmost importance to everyone involved. To protect your privacy, we
follow different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for client privacy and data
protection.
       We won’t sell or give away your name, mail address, phone number, email address or
        any other information to anyone.
       We will use various security measures to protect your information from unauthorised
        users.
Personal Information
Considering our nature of business and to perform our services offered to you efficiently, we
will collect personal information.
Notice
We will ask you when required for information that personally identifies you (personal
information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you
apply for a demo or a live account with us as well as participating in any offer we promote to
our existing or potential clients as well as to any visitors on our website. The main purpose
we use your Personal Information for is to treat you fairly, and to understand your financial
objectives and to ensure that relevant services are appropriate to your profile, as well as to
provide you with sales and post sales services.
The personal information that will be collected from you includes:
       personal details you provide to us on applications and other forms,
       financial details such as estimated annual income and net worth and your trading
        experience and investment knowledge,
       documents that you provide to us to verify your identity, such as your passport, utility
        bills, and/or bank statement or your company incorporation details.
According to our regulatory regime we need to keep your personal information on record for
a period of at least five (5) years, which is calculated after the execution of the transactions or
the termination of the business relationship or in the case you wish to terminate your working
relationship with us.
IronFX may use your personal information for one or more of the following purposes:
       to confirm your identity;
       to assess your suitability to the products and services we provide;
Authorised and regulated by FCA (FSA) • ASIC • SFP • CRFIN • CySEC                                  2

                                                                              Privacy Policy
       to process your transactions;
       to provide you with transaction and post transaction related services;
       to inform you of products and/or services that may be of interest to you;
       to keep you updated on the issues that are relevant to your business relationship with
        us;
       to improve the Site;
       to analyse statistical data to enable us to provide you with better products and/or
        services.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including
packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, sending postal mail, etc. We will only provide
those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited
from using that information for any other purpose.
IronFX will disclose your personal information, without notice when required to do so by law
or in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) protect our rights and/or comply with any
court order or judicial proceedings; (b) avoid any potential fraud; (c) conform to the edicts of
the law or comply with a legal process served on IronFX or the site; (d) protect and defend
the rights or property of IronFX and its family of Websites, and, (e) act in urgent
circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of IronFX, its Websites, or the public.
Cookies
IronFX uses cookies to gather information about your access to our website and other
services we provide to you. Cookies are small pieces of information which use a unique
identification tag and are stored on your device as a result of you using this website or other
services we provide to you.
Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies,
you may be able to change the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to have your
computer notify you each time a cookie is sent to it, and thereby give yourself the choice
whether to accept it or not. However, this may impair the quality of the services that we
provide to you in relation to your account.
Consent
By visiting and/or accessing this website, you consent to IronFX to collect, maintain and use
your personal information as per this policy.
Security
IronFX has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to
ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to
protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration, or
destruction.
Authorised and regulated by FCA (FSA) • ASIC • SFP • CRFIN • CySEC                               3

© Copyright BizTree. 2006. All rights reserved                                                                Privacy Policy
                IronFX strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for
IS ILLEGAL AND STRICTLY PROHIBITED TO DIS
                its intended use.
                You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your
                personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these
                details with others.
PARTY, THIS PRODUCT IN HARD COPY OR DIGI
                Enforcement
                IronFX reserves the right to change this policy anytime. Changes will be posted on this
                policy, therefore you are encouraged to visit and review this policy from time to time. In case
                you have any queries, please email us at compliance@ironfx.com.
                Version: 11 September 2013
                Copyright © 2013 IronFX. All Rights Reserved
                                                                    IronFX Global Limited,
                                                 2, Iapetou Street, Agios Athanasios, 4101 Limassol, Cyprus
                                                         Tel: +357 25027000 | Fax: +357 25027001
                                                      Email: info@ironfx.com | Web: www.IronFX.com
                Authorised and regulated by FCA (FSA) • ASIC • SFP • CRFIN • CySEC                                             4
